<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Love FOSS and Gaming</title>
    <link>https://jlozadad.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Love FOSS and Gaming</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:49:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jlozadad.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliens Resistance</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/aliens_resistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:49:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/aliens_resistance/</guid>
      <description>In my previous post[https://jlozadad.io/post/aliens_defiance/] I discussed the Alien&amp;#8217;s Defiance comic series and I&amp;#8217;m real excited to know that Zula Hendricks was brought back on another comic series! This time she will be on Aliens Rsistance working together with Amanda Ripley. When I saw this online I really freak out
 [FREAKOUT!](img/cat_freakout.gif)
 img::img/cat_freakout.gif because I was expecting not to hear about Zula anymore and never see her anymore. Although they should make a movie or anime series about her and Amanda or even better a movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue with WoeUSB</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/woe_usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 10:42:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/woe_usb/</guid>
      <description>I go back and forth with Windows/Linux to try different games. Usually test games in wine/proton. I replaced some of the hardware and forgot to remove the old drives so windows kept crashing even after I went on safe mode and removed the old drivers. After spending a couple of hours at it I decided to just reinstall. I usually use linux in my other systems (fedora/Ubuntu/Arch). I have used WoeUSB before but, this time it was not working properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vagrant Fedora Issue</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/vagrant_fedora_issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 19:31:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/vagrant_fedora_issue/</guid>
      <description>I have used vagrant before to test servers and ansible content but, I stopped using it for a while. I usually try to update to latest versions and use the libvirt plugin. After updating to the latest version (2.2.1) I was unable to use vagrant with libvirt. Started getting this errors:
 vagrant plugin install vagrant-libvirt    10864  19:15:16 Installing the &#39;vagrant-libvirt&#39; plugin. This can take a few minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quien Soy</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 15:25:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jonathan Lozada De La Matta.
   From Carolina, Puerto Rico
  Ansible Consultant
  Love Video Games
  Love IT
  Love joking and LOL
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infoblox and Ansible</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/infoblox_and_ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 10:09:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/infoblox_and_ansible/</guid>
      <description>I was working with a customer that was using Infoblox and Bluecat. From the research I done, most organizations out there use infoblox for everything network related and don&amp;#8217;t divide it between different applications to accomplish the same goal. In this case infoblox handled most of the networking parts ( IP &amp;amp; subnets ) and bluecat handled the DNS part. So to be able to take full advantage of the Nios modules in ansible, you need to create the DNS zones in infoblox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Ansible to resolve IT issues Part 3</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/use_ansible_to_resolve3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:37:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/use_ansible_to_resolve3/</guid>
      <description>After successfully being able to add/remove users and install Cloudera Clusters, I needed to tag on patching systems. This is a hot item that everyone should be aware and should be able to do some down time for.I could spend more time writing in here on how to do patches and how important it is but, I wrote an article for opensource.com that explains it well https://opensource.com/article/18/3/ansible-patch-systems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>f2P Games in Linux &amp; Wine.</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/f2p_games_linux_and_wine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 15:57:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/f2p_games_linux_and_wine/</guid>
      <description>Lately I been trying to find games that are F2P because lately I have not found anything that has me interested and obsessed. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m in a rut when it comes to gaming? no se&amp;hellip; Here is a list of what I been able to play so far.
 Warframe - Although Warframe is not native to linux, it plays well on wine. You will have to disable a lot of settings in the game to be able to play it the best and avoid certain issues that arise with those configuration being on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paragon_game</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/paragon_game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 09:50:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/paragon_game/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible OSP Modules</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/ansible_osp_modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 14:00:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/ansible_osp_modules/</guid>
      <description>Recently I started working on a project to create roles using ansible openstack modules. I have used openstack before but, the version I used was from 2014 and we managed the VM&amp;rsquo;s/Applications using supernova. We managed VM&amp;rsquo;s for customers in openstack but, we did not maintain the infrastructure itself. Although we troubleshooted and help diagnosed some issues with the openstack team. Issues like a VM got stuck, can&amp;rsquo;t connect to the VM&amp;rsquo; and having performance issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Mod PS3</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/mod_ps3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 23:03:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/mod_ps3/</guid>
      <description>Modding the PS3 can get quite confusing because the directions are not straight forward or can be confusing if you have not done this before or spend time trying to understand how everything works. At first I was confused but, with trial &amp;amp; error I was able to get it modded and installed homebrew and multiman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building_rpms</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/building_rpms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 18:06:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/building_rpms/</guid>
      <description>So After spending hours on trying to figure out how to build obs into an rpm using mock I finally succeeded. At the bottom is my whole history of commands and things I went through trying to figure out dependencies, building local and with mock&amp;hellip;. I have to say this is a very interesting learning experience. But, one thing I found is that everyone does the spec file differently. Some build the spec that its easily to follow with variables and others have a mix of using some variables and hard coded lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Nvidia GPU</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fedora_nvidia_gpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 19:54:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fedora_nvidia_gpu/</guid>
      <description>You can easily follow the instructions on rpmfusion on how to install the nvidia drivers on fedora but, it can be somewhat confusing if you don&amp;rsquo;t follow the instructions exactly. By installing the repo then doing the commands posted on the instructions can give you a lot of headache if you don&amp;rsquo;t really pay attention. What I mean by this is that you really have to make sure you install the correct driver for your GPU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBS with GPU</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/obs_with_gpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 21:28:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/obs_with_gpu/</guid>
      <description>I started using OBS to stream but, I noticed that in most games it uses a lot of CPU so the games start to stutter and the audio gets cut off. I started googling around and saw an article from gamingonlinux.com on how to use the GPU for streaming instead of the CPU. Of course I ran into a lot of issues since I been noticing more and more lately that most linux desktop or gaming is build with debian/ubuntu/arch in mind and fedora usually lags behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PS3 Emulator</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/ps3_emulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 19:21:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/ps3_emulator/</guid>
      <description>While trying to find emulators I ran into dolphin, pcsx2 and rpcs3. I was not sure which one to start on since I did not had the collection of games I used to have since I mostly went completely pc gaming and all my games are on steam or gog. I decided to start with ps2 games since they were cheaper to acquire( at least some games). I went to ebay and got dot hack infestation, AVP extinction and the DMC series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emulation</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/emulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:07:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/emulation/</guid>
      <description>While trying to find emulators I ran into dolphin, pcsx2 and rpcs3. I was not sure which one to start on since I did not had the collection of games I used to have since I mostly went completely pc gaming and all my games are on steam or gog. I decided to start with ps2 games since they were cheaper to acquire( at least some games). I went to ebay and got dot hack infestation, AVP extinction and the DMC series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avp_extinction</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/avp_extinction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:06:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/avp_extinction/</guid>
      <description>AVP Extinction was a game that I really enjoyed when it came out. One of my favorites IP together in a strategy type game. Nothing better than building a horde of aliens and have your own hive that destroys everything and drags the bodies back to the hive to get turned into more aliens or pre-aliens. I been able to play most of this game on pcsx2 but, I had to use windows :( because getting to build successfully in linux is a pain and you need to install a lot of i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predator_concrete_jungle</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/predator_concrete_jungle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:06:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/predator_concrete_jungle/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devil_may_cry</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/devil_may_cry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:03:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/devil_may_cry/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streaming</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/streaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 21:27:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/streaming/</guid>
      <description>I never been fan much of streaming and watching others play. Somehow I wanted to be the one playing and not just watch. I finally tried twitch just for the heck of it and I found out why a lot of people spend so much time on there. Be able to watch new games that come out or just classical games that you missed or haven&amp;rsquo;t played yet. I always wanted to make videos of the games I play as a way to do walthroughts and show others how to do something specific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Json and API</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/json_and_api/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 22:39:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/json_and_api/</guid>
      <description>#JSON and API
I started using Vagrant for a while to be able to spin VM&amp;rsquo;s and troubleshoot or test certain configuration. For the moment I was fine with using virtualbox but, I decided to use libvirtd since I prefer it. I had no idea how to create images or where to start. I asked a co-worker and he mentioned to look at bento and packer. Bento has a whole list of json files for images in all linux flavors and builds the images for all Virtualization types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Awakening</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_awakening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 16:53:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_awakening/</guid>
      <description>In here I continue my obsession of playing all the Fire Emblem games that I can get my hands on. After playing one of the DLC&amp;rsquo;s in fates and getting exposed to Chrom and the gang, I wanted to play with them since they looked like a cooler bunch. Here is my list:
Awesome Stuff:
 Scenes - The scenes and voice acting are just so awesome. It felt more complete and ties better with the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Warriors</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_warriors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 21:37:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_warriors/</guid>
      <description>Fire Emblem Warriors I always enjoy most of the Dynasty Warriors games or any of the similar series. I started all the way from DW1 until around 8 that I played on the pc. Although most of these games are straight up hack &amp;amp; slash, I liked the additions they have made throughout the years. This time I&amp;rsquo;m trying with the fire emblem universe.
Awesome Stuff:
 Hack &amp;amp; Slack Character Selection and be able to switch around Story Upgrades and level up Give Orders voice Acting Scenes  Bad Stuff: * The graphics - It seems to be a continous problem with some of this games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Fates</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_fates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:25:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_fates/</guid>
      <description>#Fire Emblem Fates Birthright
The combat is straightforward just like any turn based RPG game out there. It follows the same style as the previous games and similar to the older ones. I reached to around chapter 13 and noticed I have missed a lot of the games features and cool stuff. Like I have barely build out any of the relationships or checkout the special kids besides the generic kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:12:54 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem/</guid>
      <description>Fire Emblem on 3DS A while ago my sister mentioned that she is going to get Fire Emblem Fates: Birthright. I always enjoyed the Fire Emblem series but, its been a while since I played one. Probably back in gamecube times ) can&amp;rsquo;t recall). I started playing Fire Emblem Fates: Birthright and been enjoying the story so far. Most of my favorites characters are on the birthright side, specially that you can spend more time with them and build out the relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Cli</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/tower-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 12:51:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/tower-cli/</guid>
      <description>Tower-cli is a FOSS sofware made to manage Ansible Tower Configuration and launching jobs. Its a tool that communicates using the API and makes it easier to make those changes instead of using curl. Here is an example of things you can change or do with tower-cli:
 Create Users Create Organizations Create Teams Create Launch Jobs Change Any configuration found in /api/v1/settings/all Orchestrate with other tools and have more complete automation CD/CI pipeline  Example Videos Ansible Tower: Change a setting with tower-cli (https://youtu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/comics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:54:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/comics/</guid>
      <description>I always enjoyed comics since I was little. I did not get the opportunity to read Marvels or DC like others have. I grew up reading sonic and some alien comics. After that I got heavily into playing video games so I barely touched any comics and read mostly manga. In the past year I ran across this store Third Eye Comics and got exposed to the Alien and Predator comics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliens Defiance</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/aliens_defiance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:52:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/aliens_defiance/</guid>
      <description>I bought Alien Defiance issue #1 months ago but, never got around to reading it. After going through the first issue, I got hooked. I was unable to find the second one in any local bookstores and the local comic store. I was forced to buy the digital version from Darkhorse. I&amp;rsquo;m not much of a fan of the digital versions but, I wanted to read them right away.I have to say I was hooked right away with this series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Fedora 25</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/upgrading_fedora25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 21:52:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/upgrading_fedora25/</guid>
      <description>With the release of Fedora 26, I decided to upgrade my Fedora 25. Fedora 26 introduced a lot of cool things and I have been using the beta version on my work laptop. You can do upgrade by doing the following: * sudo dnf install fedora-upgrade * sudo fedora-upgrade
And just let all the packages go! then restart. I use the KDE version since I prefer it over GNOME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible Tower</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/ansible_tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 21:51:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/ansible_tower/</guid>
      <description>So you have an idea what is ansible and what you can do with it. After creating, playbooks &amp;amp; roles and dynamic inventories, you are wondering how you can centralize and control access to your playbooks. You can do this with ansible core and limit access and permissions on the git project. You can include all the playbooks, roles and inventory files in the same repo. But, this can become a problem once the project is git clone into the controller and anyone access to the server can potentially be able to access your playbooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Ansible to Resolve IT Issues Part 2</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/use_ansible_to_resolve2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 15:51:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/use_ansible_to_resolve2/</guid>
      <description>After being able automate user creation/deletion, I tackle on how to automate the Cloudera CM install as much as possible. I first started trying to install the rpms with ansible. I discovered the yum and repo modules. They allow me to add a repo and install any rpm available. This what I have:
- name: Add the cloudera-cm repo. yum_repository: name: cloudera-cm description: cloudera-cm repo baseurl: &amp;quot;{{ rpm_repo }}&amp;quot; # http://archive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install libvirtd</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/install_libvirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 13:32:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/install_libvirt/</guid>
      <description>Recently I installed Fedora 25 to test some playbooks and other configurations. A co-worker mentioned to use Vagrant but, my exposure was minimal. I only used vagrant to test some applications such as netbox and it uses Virtualbox by default. Previously I have used Virtualbox and Vmware but, I decided to move away from those. First, Virtualbox breaks everytime there is a kernel update. Although there is some commands you can run to recreate the kernel it needs but, why I should do this all the time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Ansible to Resolve IT Issues Part 1</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/use_ansible_to_resolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 13:32:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/use_ansible_to_resolve/</guid>
      <description>After spending months on trying to deploy a Cloudera CM cluster with over 40 nodes, I needed to find a way automate most of my tasks and reduce time spend doing this manually. At the time when I started on this project we were using openstack VM&amp;rsquo;s to host this Cloudera cluster. Although is not best practices to use VM for big data, it was our only option of having resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data on Openstack</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/big_data_on_openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 11:52:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/big_data_on_openstack/</guid>
      <description>Openstack can be a great solution due to the increase demand of cloud and more resources. But, it can&amp;rsquo;t resolve every issue out there. an Openstack deployment can provide &amp;ldquo;unlimited&amp;rdquo; resources but, is useless if is not architecture for the specific applications that the VM&amp;rsquo;s will be hosting. For example, a previous customer had over 20 regions, configured almost the same and had performance issues. This customer hosted big data applications (Cloudera to be specific) on those VM&amp;rsquo;s, had an older deployment of Openstack ( Icehouse so we could not take advantage of the newer cloud features) and no budget for further expansion and upgrades ( Including software and hardware) but, had the following issues:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>