<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Love FOSS and Gaming</title>
    <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Love FOSS and Gaming</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 16:53:16 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Awakening</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem_awakening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 16:53:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem_awakening/</guid>
      <description>In here I continue my obsession of playing all the Fire Emblem games that I can get my hands on. After playing one of the DLC&amp;rsquo;s in fates and getting exposed to Chrom and the gang, I wanted to play with them since they looked like a cooler bunch. Here is my list:
Awesome Stuff:
 Scenes - The scenes and voice acting are just so awesome. It felt more complete and ties better with the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Warriors</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem_warriors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 21:37:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem_warriors/</guid>
      <description>Fire Emblem Warriors I always enjoy most of the Dynasty Warriors games or any of the similar series. I started all the way from DW1 until around 8 that I played on the pc. Although most of these games are straight up hack &amp;amp; slash, I liked the additions they have made throughout the years. This time I&amp;rsquo;m trying with the fire emblem universe.
Awesome Stuff:
 Hack &amp;amp; Slack Character Selection and be able to switch around Story Upgrades and level up Give Orders voice Acting Scenes  Bad Stuff: * The graphics - It seems to be a continous problem with some of this games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Fates</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem_fates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:25:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem_fates/</guid>
      <description>#Fire Emblem Fates Birthright
The combat is straightforward just like any turn based RPG game out there. It follows the same style as the previous games and similar to the older ones. I reached to around chapter 13 and noticed I have missed a lot of the games features and cool stuff. Like I have barely build out any of the relationships or checkout the special kids besides the generic kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:12:54 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/fire_emblem/</guid>
      <description>Fire Emblem on 3DS A while ago my sister mentioned that she is going to get Fire Emblem Fates: Birthright. I always enjoyed the Fire Emblem series but, its been a while since I played one. Probably back in gamecube times ) can&amp;rsquo;t recall). I started playing Fire Emblem Fates: Birthright and been enjoying the story so far. Most of my favorites characters are on the birthright side, specially that you can spend more time with them and build out the relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tower Cli</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/tower-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 12:51:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/tower-cli/</guid>
      <description>Tower-cli is a FOSS sofware made to manage Ansible Tower Configuration and launching jobs. Its a tool that communicates using the API and makes it easier to make those changes instead of using curl. Here is an example of things you can change or do with tower-cli:
 Create Users Create Organizations Create Teams Create Launch Jobs Change Any configuration found in /api/v1/settings/all Orchestrate with other tools and have more complete automation CD/CI pipeline  Example Videos Ansible Tower: Change a setting with tower-cli (https://youtu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/comics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:54:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/comics/</guid>
      <description>I always enjoyed comics since I was little. I did not get the opportunity to read Marvels or DC like others have. I grew up reading sonic and some alien comics. After that I got heavily into playing video games so I barely touched any comics and read mostly manga. In the past year I ran across this store Third Eye Comics and got exposed to the Alien and Predator comics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliens Defiance</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/aliens_defiance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:52:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/aliens_defiance/</guid>
      <description>I bought Alien Defiance issue #1 months ago but, never got around to reading it. After going through the first issue, I got hooked. I was unable to find the second one in any local bookstores and the local comic store. I was forced to buy the digital version from Darkhorse. I&amp;rsquo;m not much of a fan of the digital versions but, I wanted to read them right away.I have to say I was hooked right away with this series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Fedora 25</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/upgrading_fedora25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 21:52:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/upgrading_fedora25/</guid>
      <description>With the release of Fedora 26, I decided to upgrade my Fedora 25. Fedora 26 introduced a lot of cool things and I have been using the beta version on my work laptop. You can do upgrade by doing the following: * sudo dnf install fedora-upgrade * sudo fedora-upgrade
And just let all the packages go! then restart. I use the KDE version since I prefer it over GNOME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible Tower</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/ansible_tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 21:51:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/ansible_tower/</guid>
      <description>So you have an idea what is ansible and what you can do with it. After creating, playbooks &amp;amp; roles and dynamic inventories, you are wondering how you can centralize and control access to your playbooks. You can do this with ansible core and limit access and permissions on the git project. You can include all the playbooks, roles and inventory files in the same repo. But, this can become a problem once the project is git clone into the controller and anyone access to the server can potentially be able to access your playbooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Ansible to Resolve IT Issues Part 2</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/use_ansible_to_resolve2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 15:51:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/use_ansible_to_resolve2/</guid>
      <description>After being able automate user creation/deletion, I tackle on how to automate the Cloudera CM install as much as possible. I first started trying to install the rpms with ansible. I discovered the yum and repo modules. They allow me to add a repo and install any rpm available. This what I have:
- name: Add the cloudera-cm repo. yum_repository: name: cloudera-cm description: cloudera-cm repo baseurl: &amp;quot;{{ rpm_repo }}&amp;quot; # http://archive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install libvirtd</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/install_libvirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 13:32:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/install_libvirt/</guid>
      <description>Recently I installed Fedora 25 to test some playbooks and other configurations. A co-worker mentioned to use Vagrant but, my exposure was minimal. I only used vagrant to test some applications such as netbox and it uses Virtualbox by default. Previously I have used Virtualbox and Vmware but, I decided to move away from those. First, Virtualbox breaks everytime there is a kernel update. Although there is some commands you can run to recreate the kernel it needs but, why I should do this all the time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Ansible to Resolve IT Issues Part 1</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/use_ansible_to_resolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 13:32:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/use_ansible_to_resolve/</guid>
      <description>After I was able to successfully Install Cloudera CM and create a cluster, I was trying to find a way to reduce the deployment time. The current deployments would take too long, waste over 500 of labor hours and no consistency. I could not meet customer demand for new datanodes or clusters and had a reduced workforce due to contract changes. At first I tried to find an all solution like puppet or foreman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data on Openstack</title>
      <link>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/big_data_on_openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 11:52:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozada2426.gitlab.io/blog/post/big_data_on_openstack/</guid>
      <description>Openstack can be a great solution due to the increase demand of cloud and more resources. But, it can&amp;rsquo;t resolve every issue out there. an Openstack deployment can provide &amp;ldquo;unlimited&amp;rdquo; resources but, is useless if is not architectured for the specific applications that the VM&amp;rsquo;s will be hosting. For example, a previous customer had over 20 regions, configured almost the same and had performance issues. This customer hosted big data applications (Cloudera to be specific) on those VM&amp;rsquo;s, had an older deployment of Openstack ( Icehouse so we could not take advantage of the newer cloud features) and no budget for further expansion and upgrades ( Including software and hardware) but, had the following issues:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>