<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3DS on Love FOSS and Gaming</title>
    <link>https://jlozadad.io/tags/3ds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3DS on Love FOSS and Gaming</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 16:53:16 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jlozadad.io/tags/3ds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Awakening</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_awakening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 16:53:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_awakening/</guid>
      <description>In here I continue my obsession of playing all the Fire Emblem games that I can get my hands on. After playing one of the DLC&#39;s in fates and getting exposed to Chrom and the gang, I wanted to play with them since they looked like a cooler bunch. Here is my list:
Awesome Stuff:
 Scenes - The scenes and voice acting are just so awesome. It felt more complete and ties better with the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Warriors</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_warriors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 21:37:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_warriors/</guid>
      <description>Fire Emblem Warriors I always enjoy most of the Dynasty Warriors games or any of the similar series. I started all the way from DW1 until around 8 that I played on the pc. Although most of these games are straight up hack &amp;amp; slash, I liked the additions they have made throughout the years. This time I&#39;m trying with the fire emblem universe.
Awesome Stuff:
 Hack &amp;amp; Slack Character Selection and be able to switch around Story Upgrades and level up Give Orders voice Acting Scenes  Bad Stuff:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem Fates</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_fates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:25:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem_fates/</guid>
      <description>#Fire Emblem Fates Birthright
The combat is straightforward just like any turn based RPG game out there. It follows the same style as the previous games and similar to the older ones. I reached to around chapter 13 and noticed I have missed a lot of the games features and cool stuff. Like I have barely build out any of the relationships or checkout the special kids besides the generic kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Emblem</title>
      <link>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 17:12:54 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>jlozada2426@protonmail.com (Jonathan Lozada De La Matta)</author>
      <guid>https://jlozadad.io/post/fire_emblem/</guid>
      <description>Fire Emblem on 3DS A while ago my sister mentioned that she is going to get Fire Emblem Fates: Birthright. I always enjoyed the Fire Emblem series but, its been a while since I played one. Probably back in gamecube times ) can&#39;t recall). I started playing Fire Emblem Fates: Birthright and been enjoying the story so far. Most of my favorites characters are on the birthright side, specially that you can spend more time with them and build out the relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>